thaigolfer.com 2018-05-15

# Thaigolfer - Page Site

### Thaigolfer.com's Privacy Policy

  * Personally Identifiable Information
  * Anonymous Information
  * Log Information
  * Cookies
  * Third party websites

Thaigolfer.com is a specialist golf portal and travel company with over 12 years of experience in organising golf breaks and golf days. Our website, [w](http://www.thaigolfer.com/)ww.thaigolfer.com is an integral part of our service, which aims to save golfers time and money. The site is a source of information and a point of contact or enquiry with our knowledgeable, experienced telephone-based sales team. 

We are strongly committed to your right to privacy and to providing a safe, enjoyable and productive user experience on-line. Our Privacy Policy has been drawn up with those aims in mind. We reserve the right to modify or amend this Policy at any time and will display the effective date at the end of this statement. By submitting your personal information to us you agree to our use of such information as set out below.

For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998, the data controller is Thaigolfer Group Company Limited of 99/143 Ratchadapisek Road, Chantarakasem, Chatuchak, Bangkok 10900 THAILAND.

### Personally Identifiable Information

### Collection and storage

We only collect personally identifiable information, such as name, address and golfing profile that you specifically and voluntarily provide to us as a visitor to our website, for example, to register for certain areas of the website, to seek further information from our sales team, to make a booking for a golf break, to enter a competition, to register for events, or to subscribe to our email newsletter.

Personally identifiable information submitted by you will be collected, stored on our customer information database. All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. Any payment transactions will be encrypted. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone.

### Use

We will use your personally identifiable information to service your request (and any similar future requests). See the Data Protection section (clause 17) of our Booking Conditions for details of how we use your personally identifiable information in order to process your booking. We endeavour to keep an accurate record of the information collected. We will retain it as long as necessary to service your current request and any similar future requests (such as repeat bookings), or until you request that we delete the information.

Where you have consented to do so, we may also use your personally identifiable information to keep you informed about our services by means of our e-mail newsletter or other electronic communication, or about the services of selected third parties that may be of interest to you. If you subscribe to any of these communications and then decide that you no longer wish to receive them then you may unsubscribe at any time. Thaigolfer.com will not give or sell any personally identifiable information to any third party companies, organisations or individuals without your prior consent.

If you provide us with the personally identifiable information of any third parties, for example, any other customers included in a booking for a golf break, you must ensure that you have the authority of those third parties to provide their information to us for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy, and by submitting such information on their behalf you confirm that you have their consent.

### Right of access

You have the legal right to ask us to supply you with a copy of the personally identifiable information that we hold about you at any time. We may make a small charge for providing this to you. You may also make enquiries about the accuracy of personally identifying information previously submitted to us, or request to have outdated information removed or inaccurate information updated. 

### Disclosure

We may disclose your personally identifiable information to any member of our group of companies, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries, as defined in section 1159 of the Companies Act 2006.

We may disclose your personal information to third parties:

  * if we sell or buy any businesss or assets, in which case we may disclose your personally identifiable information to the prospective buyer or seller of such business or assets;
  * if Thaigolfer Group Company Limited or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personally identifiable information held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets;
  * if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personally identifiable information in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our Terms of Use, Booking Conditions and other agreements, or to protect the rights, property or safety of Thaigolfer Group Company Limited, our customers or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

### Anonymous Information

We may collect and analyse user-submitted information on an anonymous basis, such as golfing preferences or golf handicap to enable us to enhance and focus the services that we offer. We may also provide or sell this statistical information to third parties, such as our golfing venues. Such data will not include any personally identifiable information.

### Log Information

We may log and analyse web traffic information, for example to determine numbers of users, or to record numbers entering the site by a particular link or to identify categories of visitor by browser type. These statistics would be used to enable effective management of our on-line resources and or to provide data for the servicing of agreements with our affiliate partners. Log information is anonymous with no personally identifiable information being either obtained or retained.

### Cookies

Cookies may be used on some pages of our site. Cookies are small pieces of data stored on your hard drive that assist us in providing a more customised web site experience, for example, by retaining registration information to save logging on again to re-enter a restricted area. You can choose to refuse or delete cookies by altering your browser preferences. If you choose to do so, then most of the site's pages should still work fully in your browser.

### Third party websites

Our site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partners and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

Should you have any questions or queries concerning the above please feel free to contact us at [i](mailto:privacy@golfbreaks.com)nfo@thaigolfer.com. Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page. 

_Version 1.0 dated 1st March 2014_
